<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Haven</title>
      <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Haven</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Ergonomic Keyboards</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Ergonomic-Keyboards</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Ergonomic-Keyboards</guid>
    <description>Ergonomic Keyboards An ergonomic keyboard is a tool for inputting symbols to a computer in a way that doesn’t compromise on the user’s comfort. Typical features that might make a keyboard more ergonomic that the traditional counterpart are a split design, ortholinear or columnar staggered keys, or non-traditional angles.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:25:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/</guid>
    <description>Hello, World! Hey there! I am Eben Quenneville, a Physics student at the University of New Hampshire. This is a publicly accessible sub-section of my personal notes network built using Obsidian.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Ergogen</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Research/Ergo-Mechanical-Keyboards/Ergogen</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Research/Ergo-Mechanical-Keyboards/Ergogen</guid>
    <description>Ergogen is a tool for systematically and parametically creating keyboard designs. I’ve used it in the past, but it has changed a lot so I’m basically relearning the tool from flatfootfox.com/ergogen-part1-units-points/.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:13:38 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Concepts</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Concepts/Concepts</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Concepts/Concepts</guid>
    <description>Topic: Psychology Concepts Concepts are ideas, rules, or mental groupings of similar objects, events, people, and activities. You have a concept of a ball that includes footballs, rubber balls, soccer balls, and cannon balls, for example.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:13:38 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Beaver Works Summer Institute</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/BWSI</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/BWSI</guid>
    <description>Beaver Works Summer Institute Introduction In the summer of 2023, I had the pleasure of attending the Beaver Works Summer Institute, a program for rising high school seniors run by ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Obsidian Notes</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Obsidian</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Obsidian</guid>
    <description>Obsidian Notes What is Obsidian? In late 2022, I was lucky enough to stumble onto a wonderful project called Obsidian Notes. The principle is simple: a note-taking software composed of plain markdown files with a focus on interconnection and extensibility.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Biking</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Biking</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Biking</guid>
    <description>Biking Research As winter settled in and I began to spend more time inside, I was looking to get into a new excerise hobby. I spent a while thinking about it, and eventually decided that I wanted to start biking.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Silvis</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Silvis</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Silvis</guid>
    <description> Introduction After building Tantalus and another Dactyl Manuform 5x6, I still wasn’t fully satisfied with my secondary keyboard. My Dactyl Manuform R-Track is perfect for my primary setup, but I have been moving around more and doing school work on a laptop.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Icarus</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Icarus</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Icarus</guid>
    <description>Icarus Introduction I had just finished a written math assignment when I thought to myself: why should I have to compute something on my calculator, then enter it into the computer? ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tantalus</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Tantalus</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Tantalus</guid>
    <description>Introduction This is my 3rd ergo keyboard, and my first completly custom design from scratch. My previous build, the Dactyl Manuform R Track, was almost perfect.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>