<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>ϵxplore</title>
      <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on ϵxplore</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Obsidian Notes</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Obsidian</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Obsidian</guid>
    <description>Obsidian Notes What is Obsidian? In late 2022, I was lucky enough to stumble onto a wonderful project called Obsidian Notes. The principle is simple: a note-taking software composed of plain markdown files with a focus on interconnection and extensibility.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:20:30 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Beaver Works Summer Institute</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/BWSI</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/BWSI</guid>
    <description>Beaver Works Summer Institute Introduction In the summer of 2023, I had the pleasure of attending the Beaver Works Summer Institute, a program for rising high school seniors run by ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Biking</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Biking</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Biking</guid>
    <description>Biking Research As winter settled in and I began to spend more time inside, I was looking to get into a new excerise hobby. I spent a while thinking about it, and eventually decided that I wanted to start biking.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Hello, World</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/</guid>
    <description>Hello, World Hey there! I am Eben Quenneville, a Physics student at the University of New Hampshire. This is a publicly accessible sub-section of my personal notes network built using Obsidian.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Silvis</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Silvis</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Silvis</guid>
    <description>Silvis Introduction After building Tantalus and another Dactyl Manuform 5x6, I still wasn’t fully satisfied with my secondary keyboard. My Dactyl Manuform R-Track is perfect for my primary setup, but I have been moving around more and doing school work on a laptop.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Icarus</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Icarus</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Icarus</guid>
    <description>Icarus Introduction I had just finished a written math assignment when I thought to myself: why should I have to compute something on my calculator, then enter it into the computer? ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tantalus</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Tantalus</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Tantalus</guid>
    <description>Tantalus Introduction This is my 3rd ergonomic keyboard, and my first completely custom design. My previous build, the Dactyl Manuform R-Track, was almost perfect.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dactyl Manuform R-Track</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Dactyl-Manuform-R-Track</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Dactyl-Manuform-R-Track</guid>
    <description>Dactyl Manuform R-Track Preface: This design is entirely made by QQurn, and details can be found at gitlab.com/keyboards1/dm_r_track. After building my first ergonomic keyboard a few months prior, I wanted to do more electronics.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ErgoTravel</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/ErgoTravel</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/ErgoTravel</guid>
    <description>ErgoTravel The ErgoTravel was my first foray into the world of Ergonomic Keyboards. For this first build, I stuck with something tried and true. I purchased a kit from an online retailer, and built it according to the instructions.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>