<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Haven</title>
      <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Haven</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Soldering</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Soldering</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Soldering</guid>
    <description>Soldering Soldering is the process of connecting a component to a PCB by melting solder between the surfaces. Traditionally, soldering is done using a soldering iron - essentially a very hot stick of metal that you gently touch to heat the circuit board, solder, and component together.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:35 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Ergonomic Keyboards</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Research/Ergonomic-Mechanical-Keyboards/Ergonomic-Keyboards</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Research/Ergonomic-Mechanical-Keyboards/Ergonomic-Keyboards</guid>
    <description>Ergonomic Keyboards An ergonomic keyboard is a tool for inputting symbols to a computer in a way that doesn’t compromise on the user’s comfort. Typical features that might make a keyboard more ergonomic that the traditional counterpart are a split design, ortholinear or columnar staggered keys, or non-traditional angles.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Concepts</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Concepts/Concepts</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Concepts/Concepts</guid>
    <description>Topic: Psychology Concepts Concepts are ideas, rules, or mental groupings of similar objects, events, people, and activities. You have a concept of a ball that includes footballs, rubber balls, soccer balls, and cannon balls, for example.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Obsidian Notes</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Obsidian</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Posts/Obsidian</guid>
    <description>Obsidian Notes What is Obsidian? In late 2022, I was lucky enough to stumble onto a wonderful project called Obsidian Notes. The principle is simple: a note-taking software composed of plain markdown files with a focus on interconnection and extensibility.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tantalus</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Tantalus</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Tantalus</guid>
    <description>Tantalus Introduction This is my 3rd ergonomic keyboard, and my first completely custom design. My previous build, the Dactyl Manuform R-Track, was almost perfect.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Icarus</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Icarus</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Icarus</guid>
    <description>Icarus Introduction I had just finished a written math assignment when I thought to myself: why should I have to compute something on my calculator, then enter it into the computer? ...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dactyl Manuform R-Track</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Dactyl-Manuform-R-Track</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Blog-Posts/Keyboards/Dactyl-Manuform-R-Track</guid>
    <description>Dactyl Manuform R-Track Preface: This design is entirely made by QQurn, and details can be found at gitlab.com/keyboards1/dm_r_track. After building my first ergonomic keyboard a few months prior, I wanted to do more electronics.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>KiCad</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/KiCad</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/KiCad</guid>
    <description>KiCad KiCad is an open-source suite for designing Printed Circuit Boards.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 04:59:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Printed Circuit Boards</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Printed-Circuit-Boards</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Printed-Circuit-Boards</guid>
    <description>Printed Circuit Boards A printed circuit board, or PCB, is a object that allows us to physically wire together, or route, the components of a Circuit.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 04:59:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Electrical Conductors</title>
    <link>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Concepts/Science/Physics/Electricity-and-Magnetism/Electrical-Conductors</link>
    <guid>https://eben.tonehaven.org/Concepts/Science/Physics/Electricity-and-Magnetism/Electrical-Conductors</guid>
    <description>Electrical Conductors Topic: Electromagnetism Materials have an associated property called their electrical conductivity. It refers to how easily electricity flows through them.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>